Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 15= (The Emperor's Nightmare)
=الحلقة 15= (كابوس الإمبراطور)
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
Take the concoction first.
تناول الخليط أولاً.
It's hot. Let me blow on it for you.
الجو حار. دعني أنفخ عليه من أجلك.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
You're even feeding me the concoction.
حتى أنك تطعمني الخليط.
I'm all fine.
أنا بخير.
Since the gas
منذ الغاز
was removed from my body,
لقد تم ازالته من جسدي،
I've felt much better.
لقد شعرت بتحسن كبير.
Here, eat the concoction.
هنا، تناول هذا الخليط.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
His Majesty has arrived.
لقد وصل جلالته.
Qingci.
كينغسي.
I've brought you a treasure.
لقد أحضرت لك كنزًا.
What's happened to you?
ماذا حدث لك؟
I've accidentally caught a cold.
لقد أصبت بنزلة برد عن طريق الخطأ.
Leave it to me.
اتركها لي.
Just the right temperature.
درجة الحرارة المناسبة فقط.
Your Majesty, are you alright?
جلالتك هل أنت بخير؟
I'm good.
أنا بخير.
It was the wind.
لقد كانت الريح.
Yuchen,
يوتشن،
I'm a bit sleepy.
أنا نعسان قليلاً.
Fine.
بخير.
Get some rest now.
احصل على بعض الراحة الآن.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let me see you out, Yuchen.
دعني أراك خارجًا، يوتشن.
Forget about it.
انسي الأمر.
Take some good rest.
خذ قسطاً جيداً من الراحة.
Just the right temperature?
درجة الحرارة المناسبة؟
It's gone cold.
لقد أصبح الجو باردًا.
Master.
يتقن.
What is it with you?
ما الأمر معك؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I thought of manipulating Chi Yu's body
لقد فكرت في التلاعب بجسد تشي يو
with the Soul-Pulling Spell.
مع تعويذة سحب الروح.
Unexpectedly, it backfired.
وبشكل غير متوقع، جاءت النتيجة عكسية.
But it's alright.
ولكن لا بأس.
I've found myself
لقد وجدت نفسي
a more suitable subject.
موضوع أكثر ملاءمة.
Yuchen.
يوتشن.
You like Ji Qingci, right?
أنت تحب جي كينغسي، أليس كذلك؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
However,
لكن،
she's your sister.
إنها أختك.
So you will never be together.
لذلك لن تكونوا معًا أبدًا.
No...
لا...
What if
ماذا إذا
she weren't your sister?
ألم تكن أختك؟
Indeed.
بالفعل.
You're my sister.
أنت أختي.
She belongs to me.
إنها ملكي.
My beloved consort.
زوجتي الحبيبة.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحياتي جلالتك.
(Ji Qingci)
(جي كينغسي)
Greetings, Yuchen.
تحياتي، يوتشن.
I wonder what you're here for.
أتساءل لماذا أنت هنا.
Let me ask you a question.
دعني أسألك سؤالا.
Who exactly are you?
من أنت بالضبط؟
Naturally, I am Ji Qingci.
بطبيعة الحال، أنا جي تشينغسي.
Then who is she?
إذن من هي؟
She is my sister
إنها أختي
and Lord Yi's legitimate daughter,
وابنة اللورد يي الشرعية،
Ji Qingci.
جي كينغسي.
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
Pardon me.
سامحني.
This girl
هذه الفتاة
is an orphan
هو يتيم
whom I saved days ago.
الذي أنقذته منذ أيام.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
But I heard
ولكنني سمعت
that she had Lord Yi's jade pendant with her
أنها كانت تحمل قلادة اليشم الخاصة بالسيد يي معها
when you were saving her.
عندما كنت تنقذها.
This jade pendant
هذه القلادة من اليشم
is a gift from Qingci.
هي هدية من تشينغسي.
Yet I remember
ومع ذلك أتذكر
you only had half of the jade pendant
كان لديك نصف قلادة اليشم فقط
upon your return.
عند عودتك.
After what I've been through,
بعد ما مررت به،
the other half of it was lost.
والنصف الآخر منه ضاع.
Now she has it with her.
الآن أصبح معها.
That means it's all fated.
وهذا يعني أن كل شيء مقدر.
No...
لا...
No!
لا!
Qingci.
كينغسي.
This is too much of a coincidence.
هذه مصادفة كبيرة جدًا.
The other half of the jade pendant
النصف الآخر من قلادة اليشم
and the same scar
ونفس الندبة
have been found
تم العثور عليها
on this orphan of unknown origin.
على هذا اليتيم ذو الأصل المجهول.
Who among you
من بينكم
is lying to me?
يكذب علي؟
All I need is your answer.
كل ما أحتاجه هو جوابك.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Are you truly Ji Qingci?
هل أنت حقا جي Qingci؟
Say yes
قل نعم
and I shall get rid of her for you.
وسوف أتخلص منها لك.
That will put your mind at ease.
وهذا سوف يطمئن بالك.
I'm not Ji Qingci.
أنا لست جي تشينغسي.
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 15=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 15=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪